tonight as a web developer myself I mean
今夜は私自身 Web 開発者として
you look at category five dot TV and
あなたはカテゴリ5ドットテレビを見て
that's you know my baby that's something
それはあなた が私の赤ちゃん が何か何か 知って いる
that I put together the infrastructure
インフラをまとめたこと
the backend how it works but as the
それは動作します が、 どの ように バックエンド
developer I can sometimes miss out on
開発者私は時々逃すことができる
things like bugs right I don't see it
私はそれを見ていない 正しいバグのようなもの
the way that the end user sees it I see
エンドユーザーがそれ を見る方法
a lot of code
たくさんのコード
I might miss out on the fact that maybe
多分 という事実 を 見逃す かもしれません
it's hard to find the local show times
地元のショーの時間を見つけるのは難しいです
because we've got the local show times
地元のショーの時間があるから
tucked away down in the footer maybe I
フッタに隠れているかも
need to learn that hey I could move that
ちょっと私はそれを動かすことができること を学ぶ必要があります
up to the top somewhere and then people
どこか の トップ へ、 そして人々へ
would be able to find the show times in
で ショーの時間を見つける こと ができる でしょう
their region a lot simpler now one of
彼らの地域はもっと簡単 になりました
the ways that we can do this of course
もちろんこれができる 方法
is a focus group you get a bunch of
フォーカスグループです
people together you get them to go on
一緒に人々はあなたは彼らが 上に 行くために取得します
your website and you observe them as
あなたのウェブサイトとあなたはそれらを観察します
they go about doing all the things on
彼らは上のすべてのことをやって行きます
your website and see how the experience
あなたのウェブサイト と その経験
is for them it's a real eye-opener so
彼らにとってそれは本当の アイオープナーですので
that you can see you know what is this
これが何であるかを知っていることがわかります
website like for my users hmm but that
私のユーザーのためのようなウェブサイトうーんしかし、それは
can be expensive and it can be hard to
高価になる可能性があり、それは困難 に なる可能性があります
get people together and who has the time
一緒に人々を取得し、誰が 時間を 持っています
and so on and so forth and this is a
等々 など これ が
focus group drastically these are not
フォーカスグループは劇的にこれらはありません
your real diehard users right though
あなたの本当の強固なユーザー
there are analytics you can use like
あなた が好きなように使用できる 分析があります
Google Analytics and that service allows
Google Analytics とそのサービスでは
you to kind of see a breakdown of how
どのように内訳を見るか
look from you know what did they click
あなたから見て彼らは何をクリックしたのか知っている
on what did they do while they're on
彼らがしている間彼らは何をしましたか
your website but you need to be able to
あなたのウェブサイトがあなたができるようにする必要があります
generate reports and figure it out would
う レポートを生成 し、それを把握
it be nice if you could put a camera
あなたがカメラを置くことが できればそれはいいことだ
over the shoulder of every single person
一人ひとりの 肩越しに
who goes to your website and see what
誰があなたのウェブサイトに行き、 何を見 ます
they go through right what they click on
彼らは 彼らがクリックしたもの を 正しく 通り抜ける
see if they get frustrated or doesn't
彼らが欲求不満になるかどうかを確認
start rage clicking because they can't
彼らはできないので激怒のクリックを開始
bind what's going on and I can't figure
何が起こっているのかを見極める
out why the button doesn't work wouldn't
ボタンが動作しない理由を出ていないだろう
that be nice
それ はいい
cool is there a way there is a way does
クールなん 方法がある 方法があります
we're not going to be all creepy and put
私たちは皆気味が悪くなるつもりはないだろう
a camera there that's not how this works
そこにカメラがあるので、これは うまくいき ません。
but we're going to look at a service
しかし、私たちは サービスを見る つもりです
tonight that starts out as a free
今夜は無料で始まります
service and what I mean by that is if
サービスと私 がそれ によって意味する ものは
you've got a blog if you've got a
あなたが持っている ならあなたはブログを持っています
website that doesn't have an
ないウェブサイト
astronomical amount of traffic you're
あなたがしている トラフィックの天文学量
going to be able to use the free service
無料サービスを利用できるようになる
absolutely fine now if you're a bigger
あなたがもっと大きいなら 今絶対に大丈夫
site say a news site that gets millions
サイトは何百万もの ニュースサイト を 言う
of hits well then you're going to want
ヒット数が多い場合は、必要になります
invest in paying for their commercial
コマーシャルの支払いに投資する
services that's cool
かっこいいサービス
now they do offer a free trial of the
今、彼らはの無料トライアルを提供していますか
professional service but we're going to
プロフェッショナルなサービス私たちはする つもりです
be looking at the free surface tonight
今夜 は自由 表面 を見ている
just to show you what this can do for
これが 何のために何をすることができる かをあなたに示すためだけに
you the product that we're looking at is
あなた が 私たちが 見て いる製品 は
full story comm so let's bring that up
フルストーリーCOMMそれでは、これを持ち出すましょう
on my computer here welcome to full
私のコンピューターではここまでいっぱいになりました
story calm now this is going to tell you
落ち着いた物語今これはあなたに伝えるつもりです
a little bit about it you know is this
ちょっとあなたが知っている それについてこれ はこれです
all just fancy fancy and they've put
すべての空想の空想 と彼らは入れている
together a video and who knows how real
一緒にビデオを見て、誰がどれほどリアルかを知っている
this really is but let's actually sign
これは本当ですが、実際に署名しましょう
up for an account so you can go through
あなた が通り抜ける こと ができるように アカウントのために準備をし なさい
these steps of now look at the pricing
これらのステップは今価格を見ます
and everything like that
そしてそのようなすべてのもの
there's the professional account which
プロのアカウントがあります
includes all these kinds of features and
これらすべての種類の機能を含む
there's 200 bucks a month but lo and
200ドル の月が、loがありますし、
behold there's a free service and the
無料のサービスがあります
free service includes all these features
無料サービスにはこれらすべての機能が含まれています
now I do encourage you to support any of
今私はあなたがの いずれか を サポート することをお勧めします
the services that you use and love us
あなたが使用して私たちを愛し サービス
but I understand too that you may have a
しかし、私も あなたが持っているかもしれ ないことを理解してい ます
smaller website or you may just want
より小さなウェブサイトまたはあなたはただ欲しいかもしれません
some insight into you know the next 10
あなたへの洞察は次の10を知っています
days of what people are going to be
人々が何になるだろう何日
doing on your website because you just
あなただけの 理由であなたのウェブサイトで やる
developed a new website what's it like
以下のようにそれを何新しいウェブサイトを開発
for the new user what a great idea to
新しいユーザーにとって、どのような素晴らしい アイデア か
roll out your new website add full story
全文を追加するには 、 新しいウェブサイトを 展開
to the header and then you've got a
ヘッダーに
chance to actually have that focus group
その フォーカスグループ を実際に 持つ チャンス
with your real life users so this is
現実のユーザー と一緒に
just kind of an introduction to the
ちょうど種類の導入
features and it shows you what this
機能とそれはあなたにこれ何を示しています
service is not going to have so the free
サービスは そう無料にするつもり は ないです
service is lacking click maps which show
サービスに表示されるクリックマップがない
you basically where people click in a
あなたが基本的に人々がクリックするところで
map format so think of a heat map where
マップ形式なのでヒートマップを考えてみましょう
you can see that's interest they click
それが彼らがクリックした興味であることがわかります
on that so much that it's red alright so
そのあまりにそれは赤い 大丈夫は そう だと
that's a little bit different it is not
それは少し 違う、それは ない です
going to show you
あなたに見せるつもり
geoip and all that kind stuff domain IP
geoipとそのようなものすべてのドメインIP
error clicks which would be like I guess
私が 推測 するような エラークリック
a 404 or things that oh no this is stuff
404 かああ これはものでは ない という こと
that produces in a JavaScript error so
それは そうJavaScriptエラー で生成します
this is so it looks like the free
これは、無料です。
version is more to just kind of see
バージョンは見ているだけのものです
what's going on on your website yeah but
何がええ 、あなたの ウェブサイト 上で 起こっているが、
not necessarily analyze the code because
必ずしもので、コードを解析していません
that's another thing this can be used
それはこれが使用できるもう一つのことです
for are there bugs on my website that
私のウェブサイトには次のようなバグがあります
I'm not seeing we have a website with
私達が私達 に ウェブサイト が あるのを 見ていない
thousands of pages because you've got so
何千ページもあるから
much video there well I don't know if
よく私があれば知りませんが多くのビデオ
something from season 2 is you know when
シーズン2からの何かはいつ知っていますか
you click on it it crashes out your
クリックするとクラッシュします
browser unless someone tells me that I'm
誰かが私に言っていない限りブラウザ
not going to realize it
気付かないで
so full story is going to help me with
フルストーリーが私を助けてくれるでしょう
that so we know about the pricing and we
だから私たちは価格について知っていると 私たちは
know that there is a free version
無料版があることを知っています
available so up here we can just enter
利用可能な ので、ここで私たち はただ入ることができます
our email address and by doing that it's
私たちの電子メールアドレスと 、それはだ と 行って、
going to pop us a quick email that
私たちに簡単なメールを送ります
allows us to activate our trial account
お試しアカウントを有効にする
now the trial account again is like a
今トライアルアカウントが再びのようなものです
trial version of the professional
プロの試用版
edition of full story but when it runs
全編のエディションが実行されるとき
out they're going to need you to start
彼らは あなたが始めるためにあなたを必要とする だろう
paying for it that's the $200 a month so
お金を払うの は月200ドルな ので
during that trial version if you're
お試し版の間は
interested in you know if you're looking
あなたが探しているかどうか知っているあなたに興味がある
for the professional version sure go
プロ版のために必ず行く
ahead and do it but if you're just
先に行ってやりなさい
looking for the free version you can
あなたができる 無料版 を 探し て
actually downgrade to the free version
実際に無料版にダウングレードする
during the trial
裁判 中
with no fear of having to pay and you're
支払うことを恐れずに、あなたは
not going to have to enter a credit card
クレジットカードを入力する必要はありません
or anything so just for the sake of
または何かのためだけ に
demonstration I've kind of expedited
デモ私は一種の 迅速化 しました
things by signing up and when I clicked
登録してクリックしたとき
on the authentication email it actually
認証メールで実際には
took me to this form that allows me to
することができますこのフォームに私を連れて行って
log in with my Google account I'm like
私のGoogle アカウントで ログインする
hey that's easy enough so I just click
ちょっと簡単なので、 クリックするだけ
on it and say okay well let's login and
それで それ でいいとよく言って ログイン し ましょう
boom I am into full story so welcome to
ブーム私は 本格的な話になっています
full story folks now you'll notice that
フルストーリーの人々は今、あなたはそれに気づくでしょう
first of all I've already added the
まず最初に私はすでに追加しました
header code to my website so I could
私ができるので 、私のウェブサイトへのヘッダコード
start to track what's going on on our
私たち に何が起こっているのかを追跡するために開始
website I'm going to show you how to do
ウェブサイト私はあなた にやる方法を 紹介するつもり です
that
それ
when you first log in this panel is
このパネルに初めてログインしたときは
going to be absolutely empty so you
あなたは絶対に空になるでしょう
click on settings and there is your
設定 をクリックして 、あなたがあります
recording snippet so this allows you to
スニペットを記録する
basically put that camera over the
基本的には上の ようにカメラを置きます
shoulder of your your site visitors to
あなたのサイト訪問者の肩に
copy this code and simply throw it into
この コードを コピー して、単純 に それを投げます
the header of your website so if you go
あなたが行くならあなたのウェブサイトのヘッダ
to category 5 TV and then I'll do a
カテゴリ5のテレビに
control you to see the header and I
ヘッダーを見るようにあなたをコントロールして
should see something here for full story
完全な物語のためにここで何かを見るべきです
see that full story com now I'm using
そのフルストーリーのcomを今見ている
rocket script so it condenses and minify
ロケットスクリプトなので凝縮して縮小する
so it looks a little bit different than
だからそれは少し違うように見えます
the copy and paste but that is the
コピー＆ ペーストですがそれが
actual code that I've pasted into the
私はに貼り付けてきた 実際の コード
header for the sake of this
このためのヘッダ
demonstration and just so that we can
デモンストレーションを
see how full story works so now if you
フルストーリーがどのように機能するのかをご覧ください。
go to category 5 TV and you start
カテゴリ5のテレビに移動して開始します
looking around I'll give you an example
例を挙げ ましょう
I installed this this week and I had not
今週インストールしましたが、インストールしていません
yet added category 5 episode 502 to the
にカテゴリ5のエピソード502を追加しました
website so full story allowed me to see
ウェブサイトなので全文を見ることができました
that a user had discovered that the top
ユーザーがそれを発見したこと
right module
正しいモジュール
here that says technology TV episode 503
ここテクノロジーテレビエピソード503を 言うこと
live right now normally there's a
今住んでいる
countdown there now it said five two was
今 そこに は カウントダウン
going to be live tonight
今夜ライブになります
well 502 already happened that night but
その夜、よく502が起こったが
because I hadn't uploaded it yet my
まだアップロードしていないので
website thought 502 hadn't happened yet
ウェブサイトは502がまだ起こっていなかったと思った
okay so then I realized oh there's a bug
大丈夫です それで私 はああバグがあること に 気づいた
there I need to accommodate the fact
私 は事実 に 対応 する 必要があります
that okay the show has happened we have
大丈夫ショーは起こっています
not yet uploaded it it still thinks that
まだアップロードして い ません
502 is to come so that was a bug that I
502は来るのでそれは 私 がしていたバグでした
discovered thanks to full story I would
私は希望いっぱいのストーリーのおかげで発見
never have seen that yeah so so that's
そのようなことを見たことがないので 、 それはそう です
kind of one of the advantages to it as
それに対する利点の1つの種類
well it's interesting to me to to find
私に 見つけること するだけでなく、それは面白いです
out that your eyes are somehow
あなたの目はどういうわけか
associated and connected to your mouth
あなたの口に関連付けられてつながっ ている
that you've never realized this but when
あなたはこれを実現したことがないけれど
you start watching full story you
あなたは全文を見始めます
realize people actually move their mouse
実際に マウスを動かす
to the things that they're reading to
彼らが読んでいる ものに
the things really it's really
物事は本当にそれは 本当に
interesting Wow try to catch yourself
おもしろいわ
see if mucker when you're reading news
ニュースを読んでいるときに ムッカー がいるかどうかを確認 する
stories where is your mouse cursor I
あなたのマウスカーソルが I であるの物語
don't think you move it off to the side
あなたがそれ を 横に 動かすとは思わないでください
and put your hands behind your back it's
手を背中の後ろに置きます
actually it's a fact I see it and maybe
実際にそれは 多分 私がそれを見ることだ と
we'll get a get to glean some of that
私たちはそのうちのいくつかを集めるために得るでしょう
tonight as we look at full story calm
今夜は 落ち着い て全文を見るので
but people do tend to point of stuff so
しかし、人々はものをそう指摘する傾向があります
that was brought that bug was brought to
バグがもたらされたのです
my attention as the user in fact placed
実際に置かれたユーザーとしての私の注意
their mouse cursor over the episode
エピソード上のマウスカーソル
number over here on the right hand side
右側 の こっち数
and kind of moved their mouse around in
マウスを動かし た
such a way that I realized they were
私は彼らが
frustrated with something or couldn't
何かで イライラし たりできませんでした
figure something out
何かを理解する
and they started scrolling up and down
そして彼らは上下に スクロールし始めた
you could tell they were looking for
あなたは彼らが探していたと言うことができます
yeah so 502 huh really cool stuff so
そうそう502 ハァッ本当にクールなもの そう
let's get a look at what it looks like
それがどのように見えるのか見てみましょう。
from the administrators perspective so
その管理者の視点 から
we're not spying on any private
私たちはプライベートをスパイしているのではありません
information here this is literally just
ここの情報これは文字通りただです
this is the information of what are they
これは彼らが何であるかの情報です
seeing in their web browser so that said
そのように彼らのウェブブラウザで見ること
if you have a login system or anything
ログインシステムか何かがあれば
that displays private information
個人情報を表示する
confidential information please be
機密情報をお願いします
mindful of that when you install this
これをインストールするときには、
plug-in you can actually block full
プラグインあなたは実際に完全にブロックすることができます
story from seeing some content you can
あなたができるいくつかのコンテンツを見てからの物語
block it from recording certain content
特定のコンテンツを記録しないようにブロックする
and that's important as you set this up
あなたがこれを設定するとき 、それは重要です
if you have a site that has that kind of
あなたは、 の ようなものを持っているサイトを持っている場合
private information now our website the
個人情報は今私たちのウェブサイト
advantage to us is that we do not
私たちにとっての利点は 、 そうではない という ことです。
collect or show any private information
個人情報を収集または表示する
on the screen plus
画面 上の プラス
anything that is shown on the screen is
画面に表示されているものは何でも
something that I'm going to know anyways
とにかく私が知ることになる何か
for example if somebody were to send in
たとえば、誰かが送り込む場合
a viewer question they might go to the
彼らはに行くかもしれない、視聴者の質問
contact us form and yes they will enter
フォームにお問い合わせくださいはい、彼らは入ります
their email address but I'm the one who
自分のメールアドレス が、私は 誰 一人
receives that email I'm also the one
そのメールを受信しました
who's going to see the full story output
全 ストーリーの出力 を見るのは誰か
so there's nothing there that is private
プライベートなものはありません
that I am not already ready to write
私は まだ 書く 準備ができて いない こと
that one private thing is not something
その1つの プライベートの事はものではありません
that I really need to be concerned with
私は 本当に を気にする 必要 があること
but I could block it if I wanted full
私はいっぱいになりたければ私はそれをブロックすることができます
story not to have access to that data
そのデータ へ のアクセスを持っていない話
okay so this is what it looks like now
さて、これは 今の ように見えるものです
that the now that it's plugged in now
今 接続されている今
you'll see that Toronto has connected in
あなたはトロントが 接続し て いるのを見るでしょう
here on the right-hand side that might
これが右側に あります
be me because we're on LTE so there's
私たちはLTEにいるので私になります
somebody in London Barry someone in
ロンドンの誰か
Vancouver someone in Chicago and someone
シカゴの誰かと誰かがバンクーバー
in Los Angeles on the website so if I
ロサンゼルスでは ウェブサイト上で そう私は
click play on this and notice it's just
この上のプレーをクリックして、 それだけだ 気づきます
user 483 doesn't give me any real
ユーザー483は私に本当のことを教えてくれない
information that's identifying it's just
それを識別する情報
the ability to sort of see what's going
何が 起こって いるのか を 見分ける 能力
on shows me where they're located and
彼らが置かれている場所には私を示しており、
let's see what it shows us like now is a
今 ある ようなものだが、それは私たちを示してか見てみましょう
really good time for everybody to get on
みんなが乗るための 本当に 良い時間
the website yeah go ahead yeah around
ウェブサイトはええええ 周りに 先に行きます
ban the website now you notice how right
今のウェブサイトを禁止あなたは どのように右に気づきます
now they're just kind of sitting there
今 、彼らはただそこに座っているようなものです
on that page hmm so I can click on skip
そのページには うーんのでスキップをクリックすることができます
inactivity because it's orange down
非アクティブそれが ダウンオレンジ だから
there and so that tells me that there
あそこにそれがあることを私 に言う
are some inactivity going on
いくつかの非活動が続いている
I can press skip inactivity that's going
私は行っている無活動をスキップを押すことができます
to push right over that now that user
その今そのユーザーの 真上にプッシュする
didn't really do much they probably went
彼らはたぶん行きました。
to the website and clicked on live right
ウェブサイトにアクセス してライブをクリック
right okay right because that makes
そうだから
sense that is what someone might do in
それが誰かがするかもしれないことであるという意味
this instance so I'm going to
このインスタンスは、 私は するつもり です
fast-forward a little bit here go back
ここで少し早送りする
in time a little bit too well before the
時間の少し 前に、 あまりにも よく
show let's jump to 504 p.m. when we had
ショー我々が持っていたときに504午後にジャンプしましょう
someone from Walsall on the website on a
上のウェブサイト上のウォールソール の誰か
Windows computer so again nothing
Windowsコンピュータなので、また何もない
personally identified but this is what
個人的に識別されたが、これは何ですか
they saw
彼らが見た
so there's their mouse that's not mine
だから私のものではない彼らのマウスがあります
see that mouse that just kind of moved
その マウスを 見て
around so they're going through the menu
彼らはメニューを通過しているので
I can see they are going to shop with
私は 彼らが 一緒に買い物を する予定です。
our partners okay and came Sam thank you
私たちのパートナーは大丈夫で 来てサムはありがとう
as awesome and now see their mouse
素晴らしいと今彼らのマウスを参照してください
they're looking at Amazon I guarantee it
彼らはAmazonを見ています私はそれを保証します
see I'll see you for now they're looking
私は今のところあなたに会いましょう彼らは 見 ています
at eBay he held them it's so interesting
eBayで彼はそれらを開催しました
it's almost like and now they've clicked
それは ほとんど同じです、そして今、彼らはクリックしました
on Amazon co uk so if that was you
アマゾン では そう それはあなただったら
thank you huh but how cool that oh
ハァッありがとうしかし、どのようにクール ああ その
they're dry maybe they're dragons some
彼らは乾燥しているおそらく 彼らは いくつかの ドラゴンです
links up to their to their tool bar work
彼らのツールバーの 仕事 へのリンクアップ
bar and that's the end of the session so
バー とそれは とても セッションの終わりです
that's all that was recorded in that
その中に記録さ れているのはそれだけです
particular session super cool that is
特定のセッションの超クール です
the I moved to Amazon and so did then
私はアマゾンに移動し、 それではなかったです
the I move to eBay and so did the mouse
私はeBayに移動し、マウスも移動しました
so jumping back just a little bit here
なのでここで ちょっとだけ戻って
let's see what else we can find so yeah
他に何が 見つかる か見てみましょ う
show me more so enjoy it really is and
より多くの それが 本当に 楽しみに して私を見ます
from a UX standpoint ok so here's
UXの観点からは 大丈夫です。
somebody looks like maybe they it's it
誰かが多分彼らはそれだ
doesn't seem I haven't figured out why
私は なぜ 考え出し て いないようです
sometimes it's just like an instant
時々 それはただのインスタントのようです
maybe it was detected as a bot maybe it
それはボットとして検出されたのかもしれません
was something that a caller they clicked
呼び出し側は、彼らがクリックされた ものでした
on a particular link that took them
それらを取った特定のリンク上
straight to the content something like
ストレートのような 内容のもの に
that
それ
sometimes I go on the website to just
時々私はちょうどに ウェブサイトに行きます
check the past episodes to see what
過去のエピソード を チェックし て
shirt I've worn and older you got with
私が着ているシャツとあなた が持っている 年上のシャツ
you thank you are out yeah like now
あなたは 今の ようにそうだね
here's somebody looking at the pixel
ここに誰かがピクセルを見ています
shadow web site as well and and
影の ウェブサイトにも とと
uploading a skin so you can add more
スキンをアップロードして追加 する
than one website so I've added that
複数の ウェブサイトなので追加しました
header code to more than one website but
複数のWebサイトへのヘッダーコード
we're just focused on category 5 TV
私たちはただカテゴリー 5のテレビに 焦点を合わせています
tonight so here's somebody here at about
今夜はここに誰かがここにいる
noon today see their mouse cursor there
今日の正午にはマウスカーソルが見えます
so they're reading one of your news
だから彼らは あなたの ニュースを 読んでい ます
stories there Sasha here are the stories
そこにある物語サーシャはここにある物語
we're following this week and okay now
今週フォローしています
they've jumped up to the top what are
彼らはトップにジャンプしました
they going to do the intent oh you know
彼らは あああなたが知っ ている意図をやろうとして いる
what see because YouTube is an embed
YouTubeは埋め込みだから何が見える
iframe that's pardon me it's an iframe
iframe それは私を許しますそれはiframeです
we cannot see that they're actually
それらが 実際に あることがわかりません
watching a youtube video in the middle
途中でYouTubeのビデオを 見ている
there right below the title of the page
ページのタイトルのすぐ下にあります
so on our web site that's where the
そう私達の ウェブサイトで それはそこにあります
video is displayed but here we don't see
ビデオが表示されますが、ここでは 表示 されません
that because YouTube cross-browser cross
その YouTubeのクロスブラウザ 、クロス 理由
domain security policies so we just see
ドメインセキュリティポリシーなので
a white square now here's somebody
白い四角今ここに誰かがいる
looking at our statistics viewer
統計 ビューアーを見てください。
locations for the last 30 days and
過去30日間の場所
they're scrolling up and down currently
現在上下にスクロールしています
viewed videos and so obviously pausing
動画を見たので明らかに一時停止
there to read what the episode is about
エピソード については 何かを読むためにそこに
see what's going on so you can see the
何が起こっているのか見ることができます 。
benefit of this now here on the network
今ここで ネットワーク 上でこれの利益
now they've stopped they're on new every
今、彼らは 新しいもの になるのをやめました
day
日
there's the aboon - image has kind of
aboonがあります-画像は一種 の 持っています
stood out to them our point Linux I
彼らに私たちのポイントLinux Iが際立っていた
guess it was there Sasha and now boom
サーシャがあっ て今はブームだったと思います
clicking on creating screencast
スクリーンキャストの作成をクリック
tutorials and Linux with me and Christa
私とChristaとのチュートリアルとLinux
and there they are so now the video is
そして彼ら は そこに いるのでビデオ は 今
playing there and they've got their
そこで遊んで、彼らは彼らの持っ ています
mouse hovered over the fullscreen button
フルスクリーンボタンの上に マウスを 置いた
I would assume because that's about
それが約 だ から だと思う
where it would be and then it skipped
それがどこにあるか 、そしてそれはスキップしたところ
over because we've got it set to skip
スキップするように設定したので
inactivity
無活動
and they probably watched the video at
そしておそらく彼らはでビデオを見ました
that point and here they are looking
その点とここで彼ら は見ている
again at our statistics so we have to
再び私たちの 統計 では 我々 はし なければならない
hope that this is somebody who's
これが誰かであることを願っています
interested in advertising under network
ネットワーク下の広告に興味がある
yes so how cool is that it's called full
はい、フルと呼ばれるのはとてもクールです。
story comm there is a version that's
ストーリーコミュニケーション があるバージョンがあります
absolutely free and that's what we're
絶対に無料です。
evaluating tonight and so a lot of these
今夜そしてこれらの多くを評価する
do check it out that's ooh Oh
それをチェックアウトしないでください
Karin Jenner who happened to be it was
それをした ことが起こったカリン・ジェンナー
it that recognized that session was that
そのセッションを認識し 、それはということ でした
you and is everything that I'm saying
あなたと私が言っ て いる こと すべて です
correct did you notice how your mouse
あなたはあなたのマウスがどのように気付いたのですか？
cursor was going to the right spot and
カーソルが正しい場所に移動していた
so what you know what are the chances
だからあなたが知っているのは何がチャンスなのか
here we are there are hundreds of I just
ここに私たちは ただ何百人 もいる
added the code the other day I've got
私が持っている先日 、コードを追加し ました
hundreds of videos to watch he's such a
彼がそのようなものであるのを見るための何百ものビデオ
helpful system not everyone needs this
誰もがこれを必要としているわけではない 便利なシステム
but if you're a developer if you're
あなたが開発者なら しかし 、あなたはしている場合
looking to build a better user
より良いユーザーを築こうとしている
experience what a great way to gauge
どのような素晴らしい 測定 方法 を体験してください
what the users are actually going
ユーザーが実際に行っていること
through find those little bugs to find
を介して見つけるためにそれらの小さなバグを見つける
little quirks about your website and
あなたのウェブサイト について少し癖
when you're done observing you can turn
観察が終わったら方向転換することができます
it off and then you can turn it back on
それをオフしてから元 に 戻すことが できます
the next time you do a big site overhaul
次回 大規模サイトのオーバーホールを行うとき
and it's important to note along that
それに沿って注意することが重要です
vein full story will not have a
静脈の完全な物語はありません
performance impact on your website how
どのように あなたのウェブサイトのパフォーマンスに影響
fantastic is that so check it out it's
素晴らしい ですので、それをチェックしてください
full story com if you love it hey give
あなたがそれを愛するならば全文ストーリーコムちょっと与える
us a thumbs up and make sure you post
私たちは親指を立てる し、 あなたが投稿 する こと を 確認して ください
your comments below as well
下記の コメント も
you
君は
[Music]
[音楽]
[Applause]
[拍手]